watch-entourage.com 2012-02-25

# Privacy Policy | Watch Entourage Online

Thank you for visiting Watch-Entourage.com [(http://watch-entourage.com)](http://watch-entourage.com/). We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while your are at our site. We provide you with this Privacy Policy to inform you of what information we collect and how we use it.

**Use of Cookies**  
To help improve your overall site experience, a cookie (a small text file) is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. It is now standard operating procedure to use cookies for most web sites.

**Links to Third Party Sites**  
Watch-Entourage.com contains links to other websites. Your use of linked websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked websites. We are not responsible for these linked web sites.

**Security**  
Watch-Entourage.com uses procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service to protect your privacy. Such measures are reasonably designed to protect your information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Watch-Entourage.com uses encryption, password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personal information.

**Advertisers**  
Watch-Entourage.com uses outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Watch-Entourage.com is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). Our website is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Terms of Service**  
You can visit our Terms of Service section that establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of this website at <http://watch-entourage.com/terms-of-service>

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Watch-Entourage.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Any revisions of the Privacy Policy will be posted on the site. Your continued use of this site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. This policy was last revised on August 29th, 2011.

**More Information**  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, send us an e-mail at [contact@watchtvseries.tv](mailto:contact@watchtvseries.tv?subject=Watch-Entourage.com%20Privacy%20Policy)
